tmginteractive.com 2011-10-06

# TMG

### Privacy Policy

##### Company Practices Regarding Your Privacy

We at Tiburon Media and our affiliated companies are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any information you share with us by using our web sites.

Certain states, such as California, have passed legislation requiring certain specific disclosures be made available to their residents who use the Internet and provide information that may be used for marketing purposes. That legislation requires any business that discloses a customer?s personal information (as defined by the act) to any third party for direct marketing purposes to provide the customer a method for obtaining the names, addresses and certain other specified details of anyone who might have received that personal information. If you are a California resident you may request this information from Tiburon Media by writing to Tiburon Media, 39 Main Street, Tiburon, CA 94920 . Attn: Privacy Rights or by sending an email to [privacy@tiburonmedia.com](mailto:privacy@tiburonmedia.com). Tiburon Media is not obligated to respond to more than one such request from you per calendar year.

Tiburon Media has established the following Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. This policy describes the overall privacy practices of Tiburon Media regarding information we collect on our site or network of web sites and through our other advertising. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Tiburon Media does not own or control, or to people that Tiburon Media does not employ.

##### Information Collected by Tiburon Media 

Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information

Tiburon Media collects various types of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies. The type of information your browser or Internet session may automatically provide us with can include the browser you are using, your Internet domain, the operating system on your computer, your IP address and the URL you saw just before coming to the Tiburon Media site, the pages of the site you visited and the URL of the page you visited upon leaving the site.

Tiburon Media may also contract with reputable third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect your non-personally identifiable information.

##### Personally Identifiable Consumer Information

In addition, we may collect information that you choose to provide to us when requesting additional information from us or from one or more of our clients. Examples of personally identifiable data that you may provide to us include name, address, phone and email address. If you provide personally identifiable data to us, you may later elect to have your information deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the opt-out procedures set forth below.

##### How Collected Information is Used

The non-personally identifiable information that Tiburon Media collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

If you elect to provide Tiburon Media with personally identifiable information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from Tiburon Media and from our clients. In addition, that information may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other Tiburon Media sales and marketing efforts.

##### Sharing Information with Third Parties

All personally identifiable information you provide is maintained in confidence by Tiburon Media . There are instances, however, in which your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below.

Your non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of Tiburon Media on an anonymous basis. 

When you request information from Tiburon Media or one or more of our clients, we may transfer that information within Tiburon Media or route your information to our client(s), so that they may provide the information on their product or service. 

We may also disclose information to an affiliate or third party who provides services we deem relevant. In such situations, you will always be provided with an opportunity to opt-out of receiving this information. Please be aware that Tiburon Media is very careful in selecting companies with whom it does business.

In addition to the above situations where your information may be shared with others, there is also the possibility that Tiburon Media , or part(s) of our parent company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. In the event of such transaction, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to all collected personally identifiable information. 

Finally, Tiburon Media may share your information as necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials.

##### Security

Wherever your personally identifiable information may be held within Tiburon Media or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information you shared with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Please note that while Tiburon Media will make every reasonable effort to protect your information, no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure.

##### Choice

Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information ? Use of Cookies & Opting-Out  
Some of our web sites utilize cookies to collect information about your online activities as specified above and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting Tiburon Media or related sites.

##### Personally Identifiable Consumer Information ? Opting-Out

You may choose whether or not to provide personally identifiable information to Tiburon Media . If you choose to provide such information to Tiburon Media , you have the right to tell us not to make some of the uses of such information described herein or may have such information deleted in its entirety. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, surveys or promotional communications via email, you may opt-out without charge by clicking here and following the instructions to unsubscribe. To have your personal information completely removed from our databases without charge, simply contact us at [privacy@tiburonmedia.com](mailto:privacy@tiburonmedia.com) and provide the name of the service for which information was provided, your full name, mailing address, phone number and email address so that we may identify you in the opt-out process. Once we receive your instruction, we will promptly take corrective action.

##### Access/Accuracy

To the extent that you do provide us with personally identifiable information, Tiburon Media wishes to maintain the accuracy of this information. Where we collect personally identifiable information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Tiburon Media should you need to update or correct that information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your personally identifiable information to [privacy@tiburonmedia.com](mailto:privacy@tiburonmedia.com) and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in the information that we hold as soon as practicable.

##### Childrens Privacy

In compliance with the Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), [http://www.tiburonmedia.com](http://www.tiburonmedia.com/) is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

##### Commitment

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Tiburon Media is constantly changing to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@tiburonmedia.com](mailto:privacy@tiburonmedia.com). While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as practicable after you bring it to our attention.

##### Your Consent

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to the processing by Tiburon Media of personally identifiable information for the purposes given above. Should the Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy.
